<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>(☉_☉)</title>
    <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://sagarjoglekar.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>(☉_☉)</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 12:14:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://sagarjoglekar.com/images/icon_hu7af283a5d9317cf38f40f4f6167b8cb8_2839_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>(☉_☉)</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social networks and health</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/modelsocialsupport/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:51:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/modelsocialsupport/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We as a society have accepted the internet as an extension of the self. The online disinhibition effect sometimes allows us to open up to strangers in order to seek support, or disclose proxies for medical conditions while being social on the networking platforms. These signals &amp;ndash; albeit subtle &amp;ndash; could be used to develop tools to understand population health, and in some cases, develop interventions. In these works, I explored different data source, methods, and models to capture these signals using methods from complex networks and NLP.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human behaviour on networked systems</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/modeluserengagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:50:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/modeluserengagement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Networked systems went through several phases over the past 40 years. In the first phase the network was a vessel for movement of data. The second processed and stored that data in order to allow users access to services that provide unique value like music, entertainment, and e-commerce, and the third was primaily powered by large companies that added social layers to these troves of services thereby allowing effective curation and recommendation of products and ads. We are now in a phase of an imperfect symbiosis between the real world and it&#39;s virtual projection, allowing offline phenomenons (good and bad) to leak onto the online world and vice versa. In these projects I attempt to measure, model, and design systems that understand and quantify human behaviour in this fourth phase of networked systems.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the Urban Exposome</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/theurbanexposome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:50:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/theurbanexposome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 21st century would witness one of the largest urban migration in human history. A lot of research has gone into understanding the effects of the urban life on physical and mental health. The results have been unanimous: The urban environment has long lasting impacts on our well being. The facets of our urban environment that impact on our health and well being are called the urban exposome.
In these projects, I attempt to quantify this exposome using techiques from deep learning, complex network, GIS, and NLP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These works have got some press attention. Please find some coverages below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast Company: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fastcompany.com/90455358/ai-can-now-design-cities-should-we-let-it&#34;&gt;https://www.fastcompany.com/90455358/ai-can-now-design-cities-should-we-let-it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cosmos Magazine: &lt;a href=&#34;https://cosmosmagazine.com/technology/want-to-beautify-your-street-ask-a-computer&#34;&gt;https://cosmosmagazine.com/technology/want-to-beautify-your-street-ask-a-computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actions and their (lack of) consequences</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/actions_and_consequences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/actions_and_consequences/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A while ago I listened to an interesting podcast called the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.npr.org/2019/10/04/767186846/screaming-into-the-void-how-outrage-is-hijacking-our-culture-and-our-minds?t=1636318769493&#34;&gt;Hidden Brain&lt;/a&gt; on the role of outrage in the tribal social balance of trust.
Outrage as an emotion played an extremely important role in a tribal society against non-compliant actors. If you got outraged on someone if they betrayed your trust or hoodwinked you, it can quickly translate into a tribal crisis resulting into direct disciplinary consequence, and in most cases depleating the perpetrator of their &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Social_capital&#34;&gt;social capital&lt;/a&gt;. On the other hand, a fake/pointless expression of outrage can just as quickly deplete you off social capital and trust. So the action of expression of outrage had direct consequences in a more closed and connected society.
Technology has broadened the boundries of this construct, and now , in theory, your social capital is extended beyond the society into the online social networks. However, the consequences of your actions don&#39;t equally extend, and in some cases may invert in effect. For example, a controversial and false rumour in a tribal society would immediately deplete you off your social capital, quickly turning you into an outcast. On the other hand, a controversial rumour may act as a click bait due to the recommendation systems that power online social networks, and in-turn provide you with an ever increasing audience. Which means you might be in a way rewarded for your (mis)behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now extend this analogy into the metaverse. Until now, the discretions of malicious actors were limited to controversial or untrue discourse and/or mis-information dissemination. The metaverse would empower these actors to create their own realities, living and sharing it with vulnerable audiences.
If bias-free moderation of information was a nightmare on the social networks, it is going to be immpssible in the metaverse.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retrofitting Meetings for Psychological Safety</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/retrofitmeetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/retrofitmeetings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensing the real world through NHS prescriptions data</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/nhs_prescriptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/nhs_prescriptions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Researchers and practitioners intererested in geography of health, social dynamics, economics, and everything in between are always interested methods that use data to sense health outcomes in the real world. If one can create proxies for health, and map them on to geographical units, one could ask important questions such as:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a) How does health of an area relate with its socio-economic conditions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b) Are there any temporal trends or periodicities in certain health outcomes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c) What is the relationship between health indicators from the real world and the signals obtained from online data source like social media (e.g. as seen in this paper: &lt;a href=&#34;http://social-dynamics.net/docs/icwsm-21.pdf&#34;&gt;http://social-dynamics.net/docs/icwsm-21.pdf&lt;/a&gt; )?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;d) Do certain policy or demograhic factors make an area more suseptible to particular health conditions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But in order to be creative with such questions, one needs a principled way to create proxies for health outcomes from official datasources, at scale, and map them onto geographical units. Unfortunately, most health data sources are highly protected, if not propreitary, and the processing steps required to translate raw data into geographical outcomes are tedious and often require domain knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the past 2 years at Bell Labs, I have been working on something that would partly solve these issues. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sagarjoglekar/NHSPrescriptionsParser&#34;&gt;NHS Prescriptions parser&lt;/a&gt; allows practitioners to mine the openly available NHS prescriptions data to make geo-spatial estimates about health outcomes across England. A more detailed manual about the steps for usage can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@SagarJoglekar/mapping-health-outcomes-at-the-scale-of-an-entire-nation-bbe0eb949eea&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How epidemic psychology works on Twitter: evolution of responses to the COVID-19 pandemic in the US</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/naturebehaviour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/naturebehaviour/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The cost of being on the fence.</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/expedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/expedia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After 2.5 years of association with Nokia Bell Labs, I have decided to move on to do something else. I will be moving into a more product oriented data science role at the Expedia Group, from a blue sky research role at Bell labs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/max/2000/1*x612akvUDJflKu7ym_ugEg.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;The legacy of Bell Labs&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with such a stellar organization and its brilliant people was truly enriching in so many ways. But it was equally an excercise in self awareness. And the greatest outcome of this excercise, to me, was the awareness of the costs of being on the fence. Let me explain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A while  ago — in the middle of one of the many pandemic-driven-existential-crisis — I doodled something that I thought captures a principle about how I should spend the limited time I have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://sagarjoglekar.com/img/Curiosity_impact.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;doodle&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thesis roughly states that one has limited time to spend on this earth on things other than living, and they should optimize it to maximize &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;impact&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and maximize &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;curiosity driven learning&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. But a corollary of this principle is that it is extremly hard, if not impossible, to maximize both at the same time, without sacrificing other facets of life. In other words, maximizing both requires walking up the line at 45 degrees (which I call the fence) to the very top right corner. However, more often than not, you end up loitering around the central part of this fence. This is because , in my experience, maximizing either often require orthogonal sets of skills. To drive impact one needs focus of execution, and a relentless will to iterate over the build -&amp;gt; test -&amp;gt; deliver -&amp;gt; repeat cycles. To leverage curiosity, one needs an open mind and enough time to try things out. Being on the fence means you cannot do either well. This means you are not going to produce impact as measured by ROI, or number of lives affected; or produce truly deep knowledge that comes form digging deep where your curiosity leads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I always considered myself to be a curious person, with a wide spectrum of interests. Putting myself into a box was never an intriguing idea, which is precisely why I always wanted to do a Ph.D. A doctoral journey, in my honest opinion, has more to do with the framework of thought, than with the resulting outcomes. It teaches you to start off from zero and dig deep enough to discover new knowledge, and you may do this several times in a typical Ph.D tenure. This process is immensely valuable for generalist and specialists alike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But on the other hand, I have also always immensly valued impact, and the gratification felt while witnessing what you have built being used by real people. This tug of war between the two orthogonal phylosophies meant that I involuntarily defaulted to the fence when thinking about projects and time commitments. Choosing to sit on the fence is deliberately choosing a sub-optimal environment, thereby limiting your opportunities to thrive. So for now, I will be playing the jump rope with the fence, and see where that leads me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Healthy States of America: Creating a Health Taxonomy with Social Media</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/icwsm2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/icwsm2021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jane Jacobs in the Sky: Predicting Urban Vitality with Open Satellite Data</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/cscw21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/cscw21/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KAIROS: Talking Heads and Moving Bodies for Successful Meetings</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/hotmobile21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/hotmobile21/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ranking comment sorting policies in online debates</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/argcomp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/argcomp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeetCues: Supporting Online Meetings Experience</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/iwwwvis_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/iwwwvis_1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humane Visual AI: Telling the Stories Behind a Medical Condition</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/iwwwvis_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/iwwwvis_2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysing Meso and Macro conversation structures in an online suicide support forum</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/triads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 16:19:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/triads/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Has the Last Word? Understanding How to Sample Online Discussions</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/tweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/tweb/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Characterising User Content on a Multi-lingual Social Network</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/icwsm20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 14:33:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/icwsm20/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press cover for our WWW 2020 paper: Stop Tracking Me Bro! Differential Tracking Of User Demographics On Hyper-partisan Websites</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/trackingpresscover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/trackingpresscover/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Super excited to see that our paper on measuring differential behaviour of ad-tracking ecosystem towards the consumers of hyper-partisan websites was covered by the Wired news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we simulated behaviours of users belonging to particular partisan and demographic classes, and observed how the online advertisement machinenary tracks them as they visit well known partisan news websites. To our surprise, we found that the very nature of such automated profiling systems pushes them to preferentially track users with specific partisan lean more. This also reflects in the difference in the tracking behaviour of right leaning users visiting right leaning news websites versus left leaning news websites. We open source the framework and the data, to further the understanding around how our partisan attitudes shape the advertisement ecosystem on the web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The paper conjectures that the partisan nature of today&#39;s news ecosystem might actually seep into the tracking machinery; over time learning the likes and dislikes along partisan lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press coverage by Wired news: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wired.com/story/right-left-news-site-ad-tracking/&#34;&gt;https://www.wired.com/story/right-left-news-site-ad-tracking/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find the paper and some resources around this project below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to article: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/pdf/10.1145/3366423.3380221&#34;&gt;https://dl.acm.org/doi/pdf/10.1145/3366423.3380221&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press cover for Facelift</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/facelift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/facelift/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am very happy to announce the publication of &amp;ldquo;FaceLift: a transparent deep learning framework to beautify urban scenes&amp;rdquo; in the Royal soceity open science journal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facelift is a Deeplearning driven algorithm, that goes beyond assessing beauty in urban scenes (streetviews) &amp;ndash; as done by other studies in the field &amp;ndash; and recreates the elements that can make any given urban scene more beautiful. It then explains away the elements behind the beauty using metrics which are commonly understood by the target users of this system such as Urban Planners and Architects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study builds a model of urban beauty(X) using 20,000 street view images, and around 1 million votes from the crowds about the beauty of any given streetview. It then uses Generative Adversarial models, to mutate an input image into something that maximizes its beauty score for the model X.
The differences between the input and the output urban scenes are then explained using computer vision algorithms in terms of 5 urban design metric viz. Walkability, Greenery, Complexity, Openness and Landmarks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe this system is the first step towards augmenting the urban planning industry using AI, and that too at the scale of an entire city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article has got some press attention too. Please find some coverages below :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast Company: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fastcompany.com/90455358/ai-can-now-design-cities-should-we-let-it&#34;&gt;https://www.fastcompany.com/90455358/ai-can-now-design-cities-should-we-let-it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cosmos Magazine: &lt;a href=&#34;https://cosmosmagazine.com/technology/want-to-beautify-your-street-ask-a-computer&#34;&gt;https://cosmosmagazine.com/technology/want-to-beautify-your-street-ask-a-computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find the paper and some resources around this project below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to article: &lt;a href=&#34;https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsos.190987&#34;&gt;https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsos.190987&lt;/a&gt;
Link to interactive map: &lt;a href=&#34;https://goodcitylife.org/facelift/index.php&#34;&gt;https://goodcitylife.org/facelift/index.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Tracking Me Bro! Differential Tracking Of User Demographics On Hyper-partisan Websites</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/www2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/www2020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FaceLift: a transparent deep learning framework to beautify urban scenes</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/facelift_pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 14:33:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/facelift_pipeline/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Successfully defended the Ph.D.</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/defense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I succesfully &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/nishanthsastry/status/1202944689940434944?s=20&#34;&gt;defended my Ph.D&lt;/a&gt; titled &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.slideshare.net/sagarjoglekar/dissertation-presentation-203515811&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;From Communities to Crowds: Quantifying the subjective&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;. The examiners recommended minor corrections to the dissertation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dissertation was examined by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dcs.gla.ac.uk/~jj/&#34;&gt;Prof. Joemon Jose&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://warwick.ac.uk/fac/sci/dcs/people/yulan_he/&#34;&gt;Prof. Yulan He&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to sincerely thank Prof. Nishanth Sastry and all the collaborators who have mentored and enriched me in various aspects of being a researcher over the past 4 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would also like to thank King&#39;s India scholarship and the King&#39;s graduate school for supporting me during my tenure at Kings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ph.D. Defence talk</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/talk/defence_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/talk/defence_talk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges in the Decentralised Web: The Mastodon Case</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/imc2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 08:44:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/imc2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started as a Research scientist at Bell Labs, UK</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/belllabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/belllabs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have officially started as a research scientist at Bell labs, Cambridge, UK. I will work with the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://social-dynamics.net/&#34;&gt;Social dynamics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; team on problems dealing with the modelling of different phenomenon in the realms of urban informatics, social health and AI for social good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facelift makes it to top 16 Ph.D. projects across the U.K. @ EPSRC Pioneers Competition</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/connectednations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/connectednations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our project &lt;strong&gt;FaceLift: A deeplearning pipeline to beautify urban spaces&lt;/strong&gt;, has been shortlisted in the highly selective EPSRC Pioneers competetion. We are one of the top 16 Ph.D. projects around U.K. It stands in the top 4 projects among the creative computing category. &lt;strong&gt;Please find the full announcement &lt;a href=&#34;https://epsrc.ukri.org/newsevents/news/connectednationpioneers18/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapping and Visualizing Deep-Learning Urban Beautification</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/facelift_dataviz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 14:33:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/facelift_dataviz/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netsys lab&#39;s deep learning capability upgraded through Nvidia GPU Grant</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/nvidiagrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 12:14:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/nvidiagrant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have receieved the Nvidia GPU seed grant, which I wrote on my Lab&#39;s behalf. The award would increase &lt;a href=&#34;https://nms.kcl.ac.uk/netsys/datasets&#34;&gt;Netsys&#39;s&lt;/a&gt; compute infrastructure with the help of a Nvidia Titan Xp GPU for our deep learning needs&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do online communities of people with long-term conditions function and evolve? Network analysis of the structure and dynamics of the Asthma UK and British Lung Foundation (BLF) online communities.</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/jmir2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 16:19:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/jmir2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTR_workshop</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/talk/ctr_workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/talk/ctr_workshop/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illuminating an ecosystem of partisan websites</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/www2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 12:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/www2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like at First Sight: Understanding User Engagement with the World of Microvideos</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/socinfo17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 08:44:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/socinfo17/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SocInfo2017</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/talk/socinfo2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 16:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/talk/socinfo2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WWW 2018 work covered by Buzzfeed</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/partisanecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 11:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/partisanecosystem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our work done on ecosystem of hyper partisan news sources has been covered by Buzzfeed news. The full article can be found here &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/craigsilverman/inside-the-partisan-fight-for-your-news-feed&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structure and dynamics of online patients’ communities: the case of Asthma UK and BLF online fora</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/structureoffora/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 08:52:23 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/structureoffora/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust transcoding resistant watermarking for H.264 standard</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/mtap2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 13:09:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/mtap2012/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Innovative System for Remote and Automated Testing of Mobile Phone Applications</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/srii2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 09:01:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/publication/srii2012/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
