<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News |  (☉_☉)  </title>
    <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/tags/news/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://sagarjoglekar.com/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>News</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 12:14:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://sagarjoglekar.com/images/icon_hu7af283a5d9317cf38f40f4f6167b8cb8_2839_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/tags/news/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press cover for our WWW 2020 paper: Stop Tracking Me Bro! Differential Tracking Of User Demographics On Hyper-partisan Websites</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/trackingpresscover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/trackingpresscover/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Super excited to see that our paper on measuring differential behaviour of ad-tracking ecosystem towards the consumers of hyper-partisan websites was covered by the Wired news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we simulated behaviours of users belonging to particular partisan and demographic classes, and observed how the online advertisement machinenary tracks them as they visit well known partisan news websites. To our surprise, we found that the very nature of such automated profiling systems pushes them to preferentially track users with specific partisan lean more. This also reflects in the difference in the tracking behaviour of right leaning users visiting right leaning news websites versus left leaning news websites. We open source the framework and the data, to further the understanding around how our partisan attitudes shape the advertisement ecosystem on the web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The paper conjectures that the partisan nature of today&#39;s news ecosystem might actually seep into the tracking machinery; over time learning the likes and dislikes along partisan lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press coverage by Wired news: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wired.com/story/right-left-news-site-ad-tracking/&#34;&gt;https://www.wired.com/story/right-left-news-site-ad-tracking/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find the paper and some resources around this project below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to article: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/pdf/10.1145/3366423.3380221&#34;&gt;https://dl.acm.org/doi/pdf/10.1145/3366423.3380221&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press cover for Facelift</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/facelift/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/facelift/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am very happy to announce the publication of &amp;ldquo;FaceLift: a transparent deep learning framework to beautify urban scenes&amp;rdquo; in the Royal soceity open science journal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facelift is a Deeplearning driven algorithm, that goes beyond assessing beauty in urban scenes (streetviews) &amp;ndash; as done by other studies in the field &amp;ndash; and recreates the elements that can make any given urban scene more beautiful. It then explains away the elements behind the beauty using metrics which are commonly understood by the target users of this system such as Urban Planners and Architects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study builds a model of urban beauty(X) using 20,000 street view images, and around 1 million votes from the crowds about the beauty of any given streetview. It then uses Generative Adversarial models, to mutate an input image into something that maximizes its beauty score for the model X.
The differences between the input and the output urban scenes are then explained using computer vision algorithms in terms of 5 urban design metric viz. Walkability, Greenery, Complexity, Openness and Landmarks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe this system is the first step towards augmenting the urban planning industry using AI, and that too at the scale of an entire city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article has got some press attention too. Please find some coverages below :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast Company: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fastcompany.com/90455358/ai-can-now-design-cities-should-we-let-it&#34;&gt;https://www.fastcompany.com/90455358/ai-can-now-design-cities-should-we-let-it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cosmos Magazine: &lt;a href=&#34;https://cosmosmagazine.com/technology/want-to-beautify-your-street-ask-a-computer&#34;&gt;https://cosmosmagazine.com/technology/want-to-beautify-your-street-ask-a-computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find the paper and some resources around this project below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to article: &lt;a href=&#34;https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsos.190987&#34;&gt;https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsos.190987&lt;/a&gt;
Link to interactive map: &lt;a href=&#34;https://goodcitylife.org/facelift/index.php&#34;&gt;https://goodcitylife.org/facelift/index.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Successfully defended the Ph.D.</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/defense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I succesfully &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/nishanthsastry/status/1202944689940434944?s=20&#34;&gt;defended my Ph.D&lt;/a&gt; titled &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.slideshare.net/sagarjoglekar/dissertation-presentation-203515811&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;From Communities to Crowds: Quantifying the subjective&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;. The examiners recommended minor corrections to the dissertation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dissertation was examined by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dcs.gla.ac.uk/~jj/&#34;&gt;Prof. Joemon Jose&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://warwick.ac.uk/fac/sci/dcs/people/yulan_he/&#34;&gt;Prof. Yulan He&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to sincerely thank Prof. Nishanth Sastry and all the collaborators who have mentored and enriched me in various aspects of being a researcher over the past 4 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would also like to thank King&#39;s India scholarship and the King&#39;s graduate school for supporting me during my tenure at Kings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started as a Research scientist at Bell Labs, UK</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/belllabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/belllabs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have officially started as a research scientist at Bell labs, Cambridge, UK. I will work with the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://social-dynamics.net/&#34;&gt;Social dynamics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; team on problems dealing with the modelling of different phenomenon in the realms of urban informatics, social health and AI for social good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facelift makes it to top 16 Ph.D. projects across the U.K. @ EPSRC Pioneers Competition</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/connectednations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/connectednations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our project &lt;strong&gt;FaceLift: A deeplearning pipeline to beautify urban spaces&lt;/strong&gt;, has been shortlisted in the highly selective EPSRC Pioneers competetion. We are one of the top 16 Ph.D. projects around U.K. It stands in the top 4 projects among the creative computing category. &lt;strong&gt;Please find the full announcement &lt;a href=&#34;https://epsrc.ukri.org/newsevents/news/connectednationpioneers18/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netsys lab&#39;s deep learning capability upgraded through Nvidia GPU Grant</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/nvidiagrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 12:14:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/nvidiagrant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have receieved the Nvidia GPU seed grant, which I wrote on my Lab&#39;s behalf. The award would increase &lt;a href=&#34;https://nms.kcl.ac.uk/netsys/datasets&#34;&gt;Netsys&#39;s&lt;/a&gt; compute infrastructure with the help of a Nvidia Titan Xp GPU for our deep learning needs&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WWW 2018 work covered by Buzzfeed</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/partisanecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 11:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/post/partisanecosystem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our work done on ecosystem of hyper partisan news sources has been covered by Buzzfeed news. The full article can be found here &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/craigsilverman/inside-the-partisan-fight-for-your-news-feed&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
