<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | (☉_☉)</title>
    <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:51:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://sagarjoglekar.com/images/icon_hu7af283a5d9317cf38f40f4f6167b8cb8_2839_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the Urban Exposome</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/theurbanexposome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:50:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/theurbanexposome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 21st century would witness one of the largest urban migration in human history. A lot of research has gone into understanding the effects of the urban life on physical and mental health. The results have been unanimous: The urban environment has long lasting impacts on our well being. The facets of our urban environment that impact on our health and well being are called the urban exposome.
In these projects, I attempt to quantify this exposome using techiques from deep learning, complex network, GIS, and NLP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These works have got some press attention. Please find some coverages below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast Company: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fastcompany.com/90455358/ai-can-now-design-cities-should-we-let-it&#34;&gt;https://www.fastcompany.com/90455358/ai-can-now-design-cities-should-we-let-it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cosmos Magazine: &lt;a href=&#34;https://cosmosmagazine.com/technology/want-to-beautify-your-street-ask-a-computer&#34;&gt;https://cosmosmagazine.com/technology/want-to-beautify-your-street-ask-a-computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social networks and health</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/modelsocialsupport/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:51:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/modelsocialsupport/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We as a soceity have accepted the internet as an extension of the self. The online disinhibition effect sometimes allows us to open up to strangers in order to seek support, or disclose proxies for medical conditions in the process of being social on the networking platforms. In these works, I explored different models in order to capture these concepts, using methods from complex networks and NLP.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the partisan web and its effects</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/hyperpartisannews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:50:02 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/hyperpartisannews/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The internet has made seamless access to information channels, a reality. As a result, a lot of issues of the offline world, are now being voiced, shared, and discussed on the internet; including but not limited to partisan and hot button issues. As a result, phenomenona like fake news and polarising partisan news have become a central theme for inter-disciplinary research. These works investigate the hyper-partisan ecosystem and other social media processes that may have profound effects on how democracy functions in our post internet world&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some press coverage for this work can be found below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/craigsilverman/inside-the-partisan-fight-for-your-news-feed&#34;&gt;Buzz feed coverage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying engagement in networked systems</title>
      <link>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/modeluserengagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:50:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sagarjoglekar.com/project/modeluserengagement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There has been a churn of new platforms exploring new ways to network people, and their content. From primacy driven social media platforms like Tik-tok, Vine and Instagram, to a more decentralized socially curated content platform like Mastodom. These works explore models, methods, and pipelines to measure how humans adopt and interact with these new and innovative platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
